nearly 180,000 illegal immigrants with
criminal records ordered deported from
our country our tonight roaming free to
threaten peaceful citizens
the number of new illegal immigrant
families who have crossed the border so
far this year already exceeds the entire
total from 2015 they are being released
by the tens of thousands into our
communities with no regard for the
impact on public safety or resources
one such border crosser was released and
made his way to Nebraska there he ended
the life of an innocent young girl named
Sarah route she was 21 years old and was
killed the day after graduating from
college with a four-point-oh grade point
average number one inter-class her
killer was then released a second time
and he is now a fugitive from the law
I've met Sarah's beautiful family but to
this administration they're amazing
daughter was just one more American life
that wasn't worth protecting
no more